webinarincomesystem.com 2015-10-25

# Privacy

Please read the following Privacy Policy for this site…

**Collecting Information**

I collect information from you when you register on my site or subscribe to my newsletter. When ordering or registering on my site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address.

You may, however, visit my site anonymously.

**Use Of Information**

Any of the information I collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested; to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature; or to send periodic emails.

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, promotions, and so on.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, I have included a one-click unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

**Protecting Your Information**

I implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Disclosing Information To Outside Parties**

I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

This does not include trusted third parties who assist in operating this website, conducting this business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

I may also release your information when I believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce my site policies, or protect our own (or others) rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at my discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on this website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.

I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of this website and welcome any feedback about these third party sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because I value your privacy, I’ve taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act.

I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**COPPA Compliance**

I am in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), as I do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

This website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms & Conditions**

Please also visit my Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of this website by clicking here.

**Your Consent**

By using this site, you consent to my website privacy policy.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

If I decide to change this privacy policy, I’ll post those changes on this page. This policy for https://web.archive.org/ was last modified on Oct 24th, 2014.
